# **KENNY CUEVAS**

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

#### **DETAILS**

#### **ADDRESS**

Santo Domingo Dominican Republic

#### PHONE

8292799711

#### **EMAIL**

kennycuevas99@gmail.com

#### LINKS

Web

### SKILLS

Java

JavaScript

SQL

PL/SQL

Angular

HTML & CSS

Spring framework

### LANGUAGES

Spanish

• • • • •

English

. . . . .

#### **PROFILE**

I am a backend software developer with extensive experience in quality based development using languages such as (Java, Javascript and c#) in addition to this, I enjoy database design, full data analysis, solving software architectural design problems, among others.

### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

### Software Developer, Altice Hispaniola

Dominican Republic

Mar 2022 — Present

Develop quality solutions using Java and spring framework. Design improvements of stored processes for Oracle SQL and review the flows of MsC and PCC gateway of the mediation of the company.

### Software Quality Engineer, BHD Leon

Dominican Republic

Mar 2021 — Mar 2022

Verify that the projects that are assigned to me are deployed in production with the highest possible quality, all this using technologies such as Java, Selenium, SoapUI, Postman and SQL

### Software Developer, Supreme Court of Justice

Dominican Republic

Feb 2018 — Mar 2021

Work with internal projects of the institution for administrative processes such as file analysis to implement OCR, implementation of a new intranet updated to new technologies and implement a ticket management project for technical support. In this process use technology such as: Java, Spring, Node JS, Asp net core, C #, Javascript and Angular

### Software developer (freelance), Freelance

Dominican Republic

Nov 2019 — Nov 2020

Together with a friend we were developing web page projects, using Javascript, Angular, CSS and NodeJS (Only if necessary)

## EDUCATION

# **Software Engineer, Universidad APEC**

Dominican Republic

Aug 2018 — Present